Guide to the Reginald Sellman negatives, 1911-1935
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Reginald Sellman negatives, 1911-1935, (3 boxes)
  - M[innie] and [Tajel?] in sun parlor, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1912 Nov. (Box 1, Image 187)
  - M[innie], Tommey, Slatey [Rawlings] in sun parlor, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1912 Nov. (Box 1, Image 188)
  - M[innie] in sun parlor, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1912 Nov. (Box 1, Image 189)
  - R.O.S. in sun parlor, taken by Lesher, 1912 Nov. (Box 1, Image 190)
  - Old operating room, Taylor, Steve, Cassidy, Potter, 1912 Nov. (Box 1, Image 191)
  - Old operating room, Taylor, Steve, 1912 Nov. (Box 1, Image 192)
  - Room 59, showing book cures, 1912 (Box 1, Image 193)
  - Room 59, showing dresser, 1912 (Box 1, Image 194)
  - Susie in Wyman Park, 1913 May (Box 1, Image 195)
  - No negatives for 196, 197 (Susie by Gwynn's Falls, 1913 May) See card index entries for details.
  - Down Gwynn's Falls, above Woodlawn, 1913 May (Box 1, Image 198)
  - Up Gwynn's Falls, above Woodlawn, 1913 May (Box 1, Image 199)
  - Out east window of my room, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium]1913 May 28 (Box 1, Image 200)
  - My room at B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium] [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 May 28 (Box 1, Image 201)
  - M[innie] at pier at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 202)
  - M[innie] at pier at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 203)
  - M[innie] on pier house at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 204)
  - M[innie] on pier house at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 205)
  - M[innie] on pier house at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 206)
  - M[innie] on pier house at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 207)
  - M[innie] near circle at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 208)
  - M[innie] near bench at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 209)
  - M[innie] on bench at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 210)
  - M[innie] by peristyle at Bayshore, 1913 June 16 (Box 1, Image 211)
  - Mausoleum at Woodlawn Cemetery, 1913 June (Box 1, Image 212)
  - Susie and R.O.S. on bench at B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 June (Box 1, Image 213)
  - Susie on bench at B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 June (Box 1, Image 214)
  - Hundley and R.O.S. on bench at B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 June (Box 1, Image 215)
  - Susie at B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], side yard, 1913 June (Box 1, Image 216)
  - Black-and-white print, bearing name "Sue Ford" in calligraphy, and note, "Susie at Sanatorium." Susie is in a nurse's uniform. A stamped date is also present, probably date of printing, "Feb 24 1933." B.S.S. almost certainly refers to the Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium on Charles Street in Baltimore, founded by Sellman's father William A. B. Sellman, and where Reginald was a resident physician starting in 1912. (Box 1)
  - Susie and H[undley] in side yard, 1913 June (Box 1, Image 217)
  - Mother and Mrs. H[?] in Elkin, 1913 July 29 (Box 1, Image 218)
  - Phila. [boat?] near Town Point, 1913 July 30 (Box 1, Image 219)
  - Ford's Landing from Bohemia River, 1913 July 30 (Box 1, Image 220)
  - Ford's Landing from end of Pier, 1913 July 30 (Box 1, Image 221)
  - R.O.S. in front of our tent, 1913 July 31 (Box 1, Image 222)
  - Susie in [front of?] camp, 1913 July 31 (Box 1, Image 223)
  - In front of camp, showing water [fence?], 1913 Aug. 1 (Box 1, Image 224)
  - Cliffs [at mouth?] of Cabin John's Creek, 1913 Aug. 1 (Box 1, Image 225)
  - Shore near Burnham Spring, Cabin John's Creek, 1913 Aug. 2 (Box 1, Image 226)
  - Bunham Spring on [Arnold's Bar], 1913 Aug. 2 (Box 1, Image 227)
  - Shore of Elk Point below camp, 1913 Aug. 2 (Box 1, Image 228)
  - Cousin Nettie in front of tent, 1913 Aug. 3 (Box 1, Image 229)
  - Across river from camp, 1913 Aug. 4 (Box 1, Image 230)
  - Tent from lane [side?], 1913 Aug. 4 (Box 1, Image 231)
  - Road into Ford's Landing, 1913 Aug. 5 (Box 1, Image 232)
  - Our camp, 1913 Aug. 5 (Box 1, Image 233)
  - Flash light of camp fire, 1913 Aug. 5 (Box 1, Image 234)
  - Cabin John's Creek, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 235)
  - From across River to Ford's Landing, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 236)
  - From across River to Bohemia River, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 237)
  - From across River to Ford's Landing, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 238)
  - Ford's Point from Bohemia, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 239)
  - Ducking Pond from cove, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 240)
  - Across Bohemia from cliffs, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 241)
  - Susie in cliff woods, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 242)
  - Fallen trees in cliff valley, looking up, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 243)
  - Cliff valley, looking down, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 244)
  - Path in cliff woods, looking toward cove, 1913 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Image 245)
  - Across river from [Arnold's Bar], 1913 Aug. 7 (Box 1, Image 246)
  - Across Cabin John's Creek from [Arnold's Bar], 1913 Aug. 7 (Box 1, Image 247)
  - Tent at camp, 1913 Aug. 7 (Box 1, Image 248)
  - Path in woods near Leckler's, 1913 Aug. 8 (Box 1, Image 249)
  - R.O.S. on shore in cove, 1913 Aug. 8 (Box 1, Image 250)
  - Index list and index cards, negatives 251-500 (Box 1)
  - Cousin Nettie near Burnham Springs, 1913 Aug. 9 (Box 1, Image 251)
  - Susie in front of camp, 1913 Aug. 9 (Box 1, Image 252)
  - Ford's Landing from in front of pier, 1913 Aug. 10 (Box 1, Image 253)
  - Ducking Point from mouth of Bohemia, 1913 Aug. 10 (Box 1, Image 254)
    Probably refers to well-known duck hunting areas (known as "ducking points") in Baltimore County near the Town Point, Bohemia and Elk Rivers.
  - [Steamer?] [Penn?] coming to Town Point, 1913 Aug. 11 (Box 1, Image 255)
  - North on Charles Street from 29th Street, 1913 Sept. 22 (Box 1, Image 256)
  - Hundley in Wyman's Park, 1913 Sept. 22 (Box 1, Image 257)
  - R.O.S. in Wyman's Park, 1913 Sept. 22 (Box 1, Image 258)
  - Hundley in Wyman's Park on bench, 1913 Sept. 22 (Box 1, Image 259)
  - B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium] from northeast, 1913 Sept. 22 (Box 1, Image 260)
  - Selby in front yard, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Sept. 23 (Box 1, Image 261)
  - Minnie in Druid Hill Park, 1913 Sept. 27 (Box 1, Image 262)
  - Minnie in Druid Hill Park, near duck pond, 1913 Sept. 27 (Box 1, Image 263)
  - Minnie in Druid Hill Park, near duck pond, 1913 Sept. 27 (Box 1, Image 264)
  - Minnie in Druid Hill Park, on fence near duck pond, 1913 Sept. 27 (Box 1, Image 265)
  - Minnie in Druid Hill Park, on bridge near duck pond, 1913 Sept. 27 (Box 1, Image 266)
  - Druid Hill Park near pumping station, 1913 Sept. 27 (Box 1, Image 267)
  - Minnie in Druid Hill Park near pumping station, 1913 Sept. 27 (Box 1, Image 268)
  - "Teddy Bear" in front yard, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Sept. 28 (Box 1, Image 269)
  - Tommy in front yard, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Sept. 28 (Box 1, Image 270)
  - R.O.S. in front yard, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Sept. 28 (Box 1, Image 271)
  - Adelaide on front steps, B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Dec. (Box 1, Image 272)
  - Sanatorium from church, 1913 Dec. (Box 1, Image 273)
  - Path in Gwynn's Falls Park, south toward Edmondson Avenue, 1913 Dec. (Box 1, Image 274)
  - Path in Gwynn's Falls Park, south toward Edmondson Avenue, 1913 Dec. (Box 1, Image 275)
  - Bridge in Gwynn's Falls Park from south, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 276)
  - Bridge in Gwynn's Falls Park from south, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 277)
  - Road in Gwynn's Falls Park from south, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 278)
  - West from Franklin, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 279)
  - Road from Dickeyville, toward Franklin, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 280)
  - Windsor Hill Road toward Gwynn's Falls and Mt. Holly, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 281)
  - Windsor Hill Road toward Gwynn's Falls and Mt. Holly, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 282)
  - P[ish] on bridge over Gwynn's Falls, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 283)
  - Susie in Gwynn's Falls Park, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 284)
  - Susie in Gwynn's Falls Park on rock, 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 285)
  - Bridge near Pels Station (?), 1913 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Image 286)
  - W[arren] and Selby on top of B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Dec. 18 (Box 1, Image 287)
  - W[arren] and R.O.S. on top of B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Dec. 18 (Box 1, Image 288)
  - Northwest from top of B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Dec. 18 (Box 1, Image 289)
  - Selby on top of B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Dec. 18 (Box 1, Image 290)
  - Warren on top of B.S.S. [Bielder-Sellman Sanatorium], 1913 Dec. 18 (Box 1, Image 291)
  - Lake Montebello from west, 1914 Jan. 11 (Box 1, Image 292)
  - Mansion House, Clifton Park, 1914 Jan. 11 (Box 1, Image 293)
  - Harford Road at Hellen Road, 1914 Jan. 11 (Box 1, Image 294)
  - Sanatorium from northeast, 1914 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Image 295)
  - Wilkin's Avenue just west of St. Marylands, 1914 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Image 296)
  - Wilkin's Avenue, 1914 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Image 297)
  - Wilkin's Avenue near Rolling Road, 1914 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Image 298)
  - Bloomsbury Avenue near Rolling Road, 1914 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Image 299)
  - East from Bloomsbury Avenue, 1914 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Image 300)
  - Bloomsbury Avenue at Catonsville, 1914 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Image 301)
  - Huntington Avenue car bridge, 1914 Jan. 25 (Box 1, Image 302)
  - Bridge from Wyman's Park over railroad, 1914 Jan. 25 (Box 1, Image 303)
  - Susie on Park Avenue [lady wife?], 1914 Jan. 25 (Box 1, Image 304)
  - Home on Park Avenue and Reservoir Street, 1914 Jan. 25 (Box 1, Image 305)
  - Square at Park Avenue and Wilson Street, 1914 Jan. 25 (Box 1, Image 306)
  - North from Federal Hill, 1914 Feb. 1 (Box 1, Image 307)
  - Northeast from Federal Hill, 1914 Feb. 1 (Box 1, Image 308)
  - Federal Hill, Armistead monument, 1914 Feb. 1 (Box 1, Image 309)
  - Southeast from Federal Hill, 1914 Feb. 1 (Box 1, Image 310)
  - Summer house, Federal Hill, 1914 Feb. 1 (Box 1, Image 311)
  - Susie on steps at Federal Hill, 1914 Feb. 1 (Box 1, Image 312)
  - North from apartment windows (color screen), 1914 Feb. 7 (Box 1, Image 313)
  - Road near Gwynn's Falls below Gwynn Oak, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 314)
  - Road near Gwynn's Falls below Gwynn Oak, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 315)
  - Dam on Gwynn's Falls near Dickeyville, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 316)
  - Susie by Mill Race near Dickeyville, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 317)
  - Mill Race near Dickeyville, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 318)
  - Mills at Dickeyville, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 319)
  - Hillside near Dickeyville, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 320)
  - Road by Gwynn's Falls, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 321)
  - Road by Gwynn's Falls pass, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 322)
  - Up Gwynn's Falls from near Mount Holly, 1914 Feb. 8 (Box 1, Image 323)
  - Woodburne Avenue near Gwynn's, 1914 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Image 324)
  - Susie on Woodburne Avenue, 1914 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Image 325)
  - Road off Woodburne Avenue, 1914 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Image 326)
  - Hillen Road near Woodburne Avenue, looking south, 1914 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Image 327)
  - Hillen Road near Woodburne Avenue, looking north, 1914 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Image 328)
  - Hamilton farm, Hamilton Avenue, 1914 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Image 329)
    Hamilton refers to formerly rural truck farming area, at Sellman's time being converted to a new Baltimore suburb served by a streetcar line.
  - Stream near Hamilton, 1914 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Image 330)
  - No negative for 331 (Susie on stump near Hamilton, 1914 Feb. 9). See card index entry for details. (Box 1)
  - Union Station from apartment, snowing, 1914 Feb. 13 (Box 1, Image 332)
  - St. Thomas' Church lane, at Reisterstown Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 333)
  - St. Thomas' Church lane, at Reisterstown Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 334)
  - St. Thomas' Church lane, at Reisterstown Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 335)
  - South from St. Thomas' Church (color screen), 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 336)
  - St. Thomas' Church from south, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 337)
  - Cave's property from St. Thomas' Chuch, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 338)
  - South along road from St. Thomas' Church, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 339)
  - Cave's Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 340)
  - Cave's Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 341)
  - Cave's Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 342)
  - Cave's entrance, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 343)
  - Cave's Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 344)
  - Cave's Road house, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 345)
  - Cave's Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 346)
  - Cave's Road hill near North Run, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 347)
  - Valley near North Run, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 348)
  - Up North Run, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 349)
  - Cave's Road east of North Run, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 350)
  - South from Amhardt, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 351)
  - East below Amhardt, color screen, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 352)
  - Along Dover Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 353)
  - Along Dover Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 354)
  - Along Dover Road, near Valley Road, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 355)
  - Brooklandwood Dairy, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 356)
    The owner of this well-known model dairy farm was Capt. Emerson, inventor of Bromo-Seltzer.
  - Across fields near Brooklandville, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 357)
  - West of Lutherville, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 358)
  - Just outside of Lutherville, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 359)
  - Train coming into Lutherville, 1914 Feb. 14 (Box 1, Image 360)
  - Homewood, 1914 Feb. 22 (Box 1, Image 361)
  - West from Charles Street Avenue, 1914 Feb. 22 (Box 1, Image 362)
  - East from Charles Street Avenue, 1914 Feb. 22 (Box 1, Image 363)
  - Entrance to Old Guildford Estate, 1914 Feb. 22 (Box 1, Image 364)
  - Maria Hussey's house, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 365)
  - Church at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 366)
  - Church at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 367)
    May be Massey, Kent County, on the Eastern Shore, Md. It is still a rural, unpopulated area.
  - Road near Massey [Rush?], 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 368)
  - Railroad near Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 369)
  - Rectory at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 370)
  - Rectory at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 371)
  - Rectory at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 372)
  - Across fields near Massey (color screen), 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 373)
  - Susie on road near Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 374)
  - Sitting room in house at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 375)
  - Oil painting by Stephen Ford, portrait lens, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 376)
  - Oil painting by Stephen Ford, portrait lens, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 377)
  - Oil painting by Stephen Ford, portrait lens, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 378)
  - Dr. Jones in front of house at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 379)
  - House at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 380)
  - Railroad common at Massey, 1914 Mar. 3 (Box 1, Image 381)
  - Railroad station at Massey, 1914 Mar. 4 (Box 1, Image 382)
  - No negatives exist for 383-385 (Susie, Massey, portrait lens, 1914 Mar. 4) (Box 1)
  - Susie, Massey, portrait lens, 1914 Mar. 4 (Box 1, Image 386)
  - No negatives exist for 387-392 (portraits of Susie at Massey and two "near old Massey graveyard," one with R.O.S., 1914 Mar.). See card indexes for negative entries. (Box 1)
  - Road near old graveyard, Massey, 1914 Mar. 5 (Box 1, Image 393)
  - Photographic print: Card index entry - Susie by fence on road, my last picture, 1914 Mar. 5 (Box 1, Image 394)
    No negative. Black-and-white print bears name "Susie S. Ford" in calligraphy, and note, "Susie near Massey, the next to my last picture of my Love." A stamped date is also present, probably same date of printing as other print in collection, "Feb 24 [1933]."
  - Massey, 1914 Mar. 6 (Box 1, Image 395)
  - Massey, 1914 Mar. 6 (Box 1, Image 396)
  - Massey, 1914 Mar. 6 (Box 1, Image 397)
  - Railroad common at Massey, 1914 Mar. 6 (Box 1, Image 398)
  - Maria's house at Massey, 1914 Mar. 6 (Box 1, Image 399)
  - Maria's house at Massey, 1914 Mar. 6 (Box 1, Image 400)
  - Train coming into Massey, 1914 Mar. 7 (Box 1, Image 401)
  - Abe, the nigger [may be someone in blackface?], 1914 Mar. 7 (Box 1, Image 402)
  - Massey in the snow, 1914 Mar. 7 (Box 1, Image 403)
  - Massey in the snow, 1914 Mar. 7 (Box 1, Image 404)
  - Massey in the snow, 1914 Mar. 7 (Box 1, Image 405)
  - From porch toward Massey, 1914 Mar. 7 (Box 1, Image 406)
  - Moonlight from porch, 1914 Mar. 12 (Box 1, Image 407)
  - My room at the Mount Royal, 1914 Mar. 12 (Box 1, Image 408)
    Hotel and apartments at Mt. Royal Ave. and Calvert St. in Baltimore, still standing and used as apartments.
  - Library at the Mount Royal, 1914 Mar. 12 (Box 1, Image 409)
  - Mother's room at the Mount Royal, 1914 Mar. 12 (Box 1, Image 410)
  - St. Thomas' church from south, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 411)
  - Woods on Caves, wanderlusters, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 412)
  - Edge of woods on Caves, wanderlusters, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 413)
  - Along the fence on Caves, wanderlusters, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 414)
  - The lone tree on Caves, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 415)
  - Crossing the stream on Caves, wanderlusters, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 416)
  - Line of march of wanderlusters, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 417)
  - Open fields, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 418)
  - Wanderlusters at rest, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 419)
  - Green Spring Valley, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 420)
  - Green Spring Valley, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 421)
  - Ruin near Stevenson, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 422)
  - Stevenson Station, 1914 Apr. 12 (Box 1, Image 423)
  - Fallsway from Guildford Ave., 1914 Apr. 17 (Box 1, Image 424)
  - Fallsway from Biddle Street bridge, 1914 Apr. 17 (Box 1, Image 425)
  - Fallsway from Biddle Street bridge, 1914 Apr. 17 (Box 1, Image 426)
  - Chase Street bridge, 1914 Apr. 17 (Box 1, Image 427)
  - Fallsway and [jail?] from Guildford Ave., 1914 Apr. 17 (Box 1, Image 428)
  - N. on Fallsway from [Mullison?] St., 1914 Apr. 17 (Box 1, Image 429)
  - S. on Fallsway from [Mullison?] St., 1914 Apr. 17 (Box 1, Image 430)
  - Start of wanderlusters, Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 431)
  - Bridge at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 432)
  - Maryland Heights at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 433)
  - Fence in woods at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 434)
  - Across field at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 435)
  - Towards gap at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 436)
  - Spring at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 437)
  - House by spring at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 438)
  - Over the valley and mountainside at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 439)
  - Mountainside near top at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 440)
  - At the top at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 1, Image 441)
  - Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 442)
  - From Eagle Rock at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 443)
  - From Eagle Rock at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 444)
  - Woods on mountain at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 445)
  - Fire on mountain at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 446)
  - Over the valley at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 447)
  - From Broad Rock at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 448)
  - Toward gap at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 449)
  - Over the valley at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 450)
  - Over the valley at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 451)
  - Over the valley at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 452)
  - Road home at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 453)
  - Bridge at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 454)
  - On way home at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 455)
  - Road at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 456)
  - Near at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 457)
  - River at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 458)
  - In town of Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 459)
  - In town of Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 460)
  - In town of Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 461)
  - In town of Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 462)
  - In town of Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 463)
  - Group in Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 464)
  - "Unexposed," 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 465)
  - In town of Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 466)
  - In town of Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 467)
  - Railroad at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 468)
  - Island Park at Harper's Ferry, 1914 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Image 469)
  - Island Park station at Harper's Ferry, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 470)
  - Warren, A[lyers], Sech[--d], Selby, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 471)
    These next images are of four women in nurse's uniform at their commencement at an unspecified school.
  - Warren, A[lyers], Sech[--d], Selby, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 472)
  - Warren, A[lyers], Sech[--d], Selby, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 473)
  - Warren, A[lyers], Sech[--d], Selby, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 474)
  - Speakers and faculty, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 475)
  - Speakers and faculty, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 476)
  - Speakers and faculty, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 477)
  - D.S.S.H. Potter, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 478)
  - Obedience Cox Darden, commencement 1914, 1914 May 28 (Box 2, Image 479)
  - Obedience Cox Darden, commencement 1914, side yard, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 480)
  - Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 481)
  - Valley in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 482)
  - Valley in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 483)
  - Part of Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 484)
  - Obedience in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 485)
  - Obedience in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 486)
  - Children in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 487)
  - Obedience in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 488)
  - View in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 489)
  - R.O.S. in Wyman's Park, 1914 June 6 (Box 2, Image 490)
  - Small creek, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 491)
  - Obedience up small creek, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 492)
  - River crest, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 493)
  - Miles River bridge, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 494)
  - Campbells Place, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 495)
  - Geese, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 496)
  - Double exposure, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 497)
  - Near Elevator's Place, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 498)
  - Tree on point of a creek, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 499)
  - Obedience on wharf, Miles River, 1918 Aug. (Box 2, Image 500)
  - Index cards, 501-800 (Box 2)
  - Hollow near house, fog, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 26 (Box 2, Image 501)
  - [---], Todd, Louise, Bavie, Rose, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 26 (Box 2, Image 502)
  - Elevator's Place, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 26 (Box 2, Image 503)
  - O.D.S. by bee hives, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 26 (Box 2, Image 504)
  - R.O.S. on wharf, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 26 (Box 2, Image 505)
  - O.D.S. and R.O.S. on bench, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 26 (Box 2, Image 506)
  - O.D.S. in front of house, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 28 (Box 2, Image 507)
  - Opposite shore, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 29 (Box 2, Image 508)
  - Hollow near house, rain, Miles River, 1918 Aug. 29 (Box 2, Image 509)
  - Up the river, Miles River, 1919 June 18 (Box 2, Image 510)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, H.W. of Md., 1919 June 18 (Box 2, Image 511)
    Bruce as newborn, probably born June 14, 1919, died in Missouri, 1994; served in WWII. H.W. may refer to hospital.
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, H.W. of Md., 1919 June 18 (Box 2, Image 512)